jizz24.com 2019-12-25

# Privacy Policy - Jizz24.com

Effective Date: December 25, 2019  
Sites Covered: Jizz24.com 

Pursuant to our [Terms of Use](http://www.jizz24.com/i/terms/), this document describes how we treat personal information related to your use of this website (the “Website”), including information you provide when using it. If you do not agree with these terms and do not wish to use our service, you should leave the site.

We expressly and strictly limit use of the Website to adults over 18 years of age or the age of majority in the individual’s jurisdiction, whichever is greater. Anyone under this age is strictly forbidden from using the Website. We do not knowingly seek or collect any personal information or data from persons who have not attained this age.

This Privacy Policy can provide privacy details on how we manage your personal information.

Please take a moment to familiarize yourself with our privacy practices and let us know if you have any questions.

  * I.  **Collection of Information**

We collect, process and retain personal data to the extent it is necessary to provide users with our service, especially for the following purposes, e.g. keeping search and video preferences, keeping the likes of users, displaying advertisements, keeping statistics, etc.

We do not collect, process or retain personal data unless allowed under statutory laws, required by a judicial or governmental order. We collect all personal data by ourselves and by our means. 

The only personal data we collect from users are their Geo-location (Country), Browser language, Operating System and Referer sites the users came from.

**WE DO NOT STORE PERSONAL DATA!**

All collected information is only used to customize content and advertising and prepare aggregate statistics about the overall activity on the site. Such aggregate statistics include the countries visitors came from and the types of electronic device used; they do not contain any personal information.

We do not track every click or video watched by users and associate that with the particular user. We collect only agrregated data of total clicks and views that were made for every piece of content without data about users that did that clicks.

_**We repeat: WE DO NOT COLLECT OR STORE USER PERSONAL DATA!**_

We get info to customize search results, give you a cookie with needed parameters and then delete all personal data.

  * II.  **Use of Information**

We use information to provide, enhance and personalize our services and marketing efforts:

    * \- provide localized content (site language);

    * \- provide customized and personalized viewing recommendations for videos we think will be enjoyable;

    * \- customize advertising you view;

    * \- analyze and understand our audience, improve our service (including our user interface experiences) and optimize content selection, recommendation algorithms and delivery;

    * \- prevent potentially illegal or harmful activities, including fraud.

  * III.  **Disclosure of Information**

We disclose your information for certain purposes to third parties, as described below:

    * _Service Providers._ We may share the information collected about you with companies that provide services to us and our business partners, including companies that assist with analytics (Google Analitycs service), hosting, customer and technical support service

    * _Advertisers and Advertising-Related Service Providers._ We may share the information about you with advertisers and service providers that perform advertising-related services for us and our business partners in order to tailor advertisements, measure and improve advertising effectiveness, and enable other enhancements. This information includes:

      * \- Browser user agent;
      * \- IP address of the user;
      * \- Geo-location (Country);
      * \- Browser language;
      * \- Operating System;
      * \- Support for JavaScript.
    * All that information may be collected by Advertising-Related Service Providers (ARSP) using standard data scripts and can be used to optimize banner advertising shown on our site. We do not collect or store such data and cooperate with reliable and trusted ARSP only:

      * \- Exoclick Ltd. operates under the following terms: 
        * Terms of Service: <https://www.exoclick.com/terms-conditions/>
        * Privacy Policy: <https://www.exoclick.com/privacy/>
      * \- Ero-Advertising Company operates under the following terms: 
        * Terms of Service: <http://ero-advertising.com/#!/terms>
        * Privacy Policy: <http://ero-advertising.com/#!/privacy>
      * \- TrafficStars Company operates under the following terms: 
        * Terms of Service: <https://trafficstars.com/terms-conditions/>
        * Privacy Policy: <https://trafficstars.com/privacy-policy/>
  * IV.  **Cookies and Google Analytics**

    * We use cookies to collect information about how this site is used.

    * Cookies are text files that are placed by the browser in the memory of a user's device when this site is visited. While working we use session cookies and persistent cookies:

      * \- Session cookies expire at the end of a browser session. They only enable us to collect and connect the user’s actions during the particular browser session and are deleted when the browser is closed.
      * \- Persistent cookies survive a browser session and are stored for a predefined period of time (3 days). We are using persistent cookies with the following information and for the following purposes: 
        * \- Keeping search preferences and list of videos the user viewed;
        * \- Keeping the likes of users;
        * \- Displaying the advertisements;
        * \- Keeping statistics regarding the speed loading of the pages.
    * The user can disable the cookie function in his browser options. Please see the specific information of the browser used for visiting this website. For details how to control and/or delete cookies, see aboutcookies.org. If cookies are disabled the user might not be able to use all the functions and services of our site.

  * V.  **Information security**

    * Note that all data is kept in a secure environment on our main servers located in Europe. Only restricted access is provided to a limited number of our employees who are bound to keep all information confidential.

    * We work hard to protect our users from unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of information we hold. In particular:

      * \- We encrypt our services using SSL.
      * \- We do not store personal information of particular user. We aggregate user behavior data to get statistics and delete all personal information at the moment.
      * \- We review our information collection, storage and processing practices, including physical security measures, to guard against unauthorized access to systems.
      * \- We restrict access to personal information to our employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to process it for us, and who are subject to strict contractual confidentiality obligations and may be disciplined or terminated if they fail to meet these obligations.
  * VI.  **When this Privacy Policy applies**

    * Our Privacy Policy applies to all of the services offered by our site, but excludes services that have separate privacy policies that do not incorporate this Privacy Policy.

    * Our Privacy Policy does not apply to services offered by other companies or individuals, including sites that may be displayed to you if you leave our site or other sites linked from our services. Our Privacy Policy does not cover the information practices of other companies and organizations who advertise our services, and who may use cookies, pixel tags and other technologies to serve and offer relevant ads.
